Copelof, Maxwell Arbitration Briefs, Exhibits, Transcripts and Decisions 5129
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Anton Machine Works, Brooklyn, NY vs. United Coin, Machine Employees Union, New York, NY., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  10/7/42. Issue: hiring - hiring halls & union referral.
- Argonne Worsted Co., Inc., Woonsocket, RI vs. Industrial Trades Union., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  5/3/47. Issue: transfers - seniority.
- Argonne Worsted Co., Inc., Woonsocket, RI vs. Industrial Trades Union., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  7/23/46. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Argonne Worsted Co., Inc., Woonsocket, RI vs. Industrial Trades Union., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  1/17/46. Issue: union representatives & business - maintenance of membership.
- Arkwright Corp., Fall River, MA vs. TWUA, Local 1057., 1943 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  6/19/43. Issue: rates of pay - increases
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. UTWA, Dept. of Woolen & Worsted Workers, Local 1113., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  10/8/46. Issue: seniority - super seniority.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. Federation of Woolen & Worsted Workers, AF of L, Local 1113., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  6/15/45. Overtime - failure to assign.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. UTWA, Dept. of Woolen & Worsted Workers, Local 1113., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  4/9/48. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. UTWA, Dept. of Woolen & Worsted Workers, Local 1113., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  4/5/48. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. UTWA, Dept. of Woolen & Worsted Workers, Local 1113., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  3/4/48. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment. no decision.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. UTWA, Dept. of Woolen & Worsted Workers, Local 1113., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  7/17/46. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. UTWA, Dept. of Woolen & Worsted Workers, Local 1113., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  6/22/46. Issue: standards of production - workload and supplemental decision 11/1/46.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. UTWA, Dept. of Woolen & Worsted Workers, Local 1113., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  6/20/46. Issue: standards of production - workload.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. UTWA, Dept. of Woolen & Worsted Workers, Local 1113., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  6/20/46. Issue: rates of pay - bonuses.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. UTWA, Dept. of Woolen & Worsted Workers, Local 1113., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  6/20/46. Issue: rates of pay - method of payment.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. UTWA, Dept. of Woolen & Worsted Workers, Local 1113., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  5/11/46. Issue: rates of pay - increase and supplemental 5/11/46.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. UTWA, Dept. of Woolen & Worsted Workers, Local 1113., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  1/22/46. Issue: standards of production - workload.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. UTWA, Dept. of Woolen & Worsted Workers, Local 1113., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  10/18/45. Issue: rates of pay.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. UTWA, Dept. of Woolen & Worsted Workers, Local 1113., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  6/2/48. Issue: rates of pay - bonus.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. Federation of Woolen & Worsted Workers, AF of L, Local 1113., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  6/15/45. Issue: rates of pay.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. Federation of Woolen & Worsted Workers, AF of L, Local 1113., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  6/13/45. Issue: rates of pay - equal pay for equal work.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. Federation of Woolen & Worsted Workers, AF of L, Local 1113., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  3/26/45. Issue: rates of pay - shift differentials.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. Federation of Woolen & Worsted Workers, AF of L, Local 1113., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  3/17/45. Issue: rates of pay - shift differentials.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. Federation of Woolen & Worsted Workers, AF of L, Local 1113., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  2/12/45. Issue: rates of pay.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. Federation of Woolen & Worsted Workers, AF of L, Local 1113., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  12/13/44. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. Federation of Woolen & Worsted Workers, AF of L, Local 1113., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  6/2/44. Issue: rates of pay.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. Federation of Woolen & Worsted Workers, AF of L, Local 1113., 1943 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  11/17/43. Issue: rates of pay.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. Federation of Woolen & Worsted Workers, AF of L, Local 1113., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  6/15/93. Issue: rates of pay.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. Federation of Woolen & Worsted Workers, AF of L, Local 1113., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  9/9/42. Issue: standards of production - workload; rates of pay.
- Arlington Mills, Lawrence, MA vs. UTWA, Dept. of Woolen & Worsted Workers, Local 1113., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  1/22/46. Issue: classification of jobs - upgrading and clarification 1/22/46.
- Armory Worsted Mills, Manchester, NH vs. TWUA, Local 560, 864, 897., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  9/7/48. Issue: vacations - eligibility; vacation pay - eligibility.
- Armory Worsted Mills, Manchester, NH vs. TWUA, Local 897., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  3/17/47. Issue: rates of pay - reduction.
- Armory Worsted Mills, Manchester, NH vs. TWUA, Local 560-B., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  3/14/47. Issue: rates of pay - piecework vs. day work.
- Armory Worsted Mills, Manchester, NH vs. TWUA, Local 560-B., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Armory Worsted Mills, Manchester, NH vs. TWUA, Local 560-B., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  3/27/47. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Armory Worsted Mills, Manchester, NH vs. TWUA, Local 897., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  2/5/48. Issue: management rights - incentive pay & incentive systems.
- Arnel Co., Inc., New York, NY vs. UFW, Local 458., 1940 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  9/23/40. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Art Chrome Co. of America vs. UFW, Local 136B., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  5/19/41. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Art Chrome Co. of America vs. UFW, Local 136B., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  1/14/42. Issue: withdrawn.
- Art Chrome Co. of America vs. UFW, Local 136., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  4/18/42. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Art Chrome Co. of America vs. UFW, Local 136B., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  5/13/44. Issue: interest arbitration - contract modification.
- Ashaway Woolen Mills, Inc. Ashaway, RI vs. TWUA, Local 586., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  8/11/47. Issue: layoff - vacation pay.
- Ashland Corp., Jewett City, CT vs. TWUA, Local 60., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  10/4/46. Issue: classification of jobs - duties performed.
- Aspinook Corp., Easthampton, MA vs. TWUA, Local 775., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  10/14/47. Issue: holiday & holiday pay.
- Associated Corset & Brassiere Manufacturers, Inc. vs. Int'l. Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) Corsett & Brassiere Workers of NY, Local 32., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  1/23/42. Issue: rates of pay - probationary employees.
- Associated Dress Manufacturers Assoc., Boston, MA vs. ILGWU, Joint Board of Cloak, Skirt & Dressmakers Union., Locals 12, 33, 39, 46, 56, 73 and 80., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  12/10/46. Issue: rates of pay - increase
- Associated Dress Manufacturers Assoc., Boston, MA vs. ILGWU, Joint Board of Cloak, Skirt & Dressmakers Union., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  11/13/45. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Associated Shoe Industries, Inc. vs. Brotherhood of Shoe & Allied Craftsmen, Cut Sole Local., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  8/19/46. Issue: supervisors & foremen - inclusion in bargaining unit.
- Associated Shoe Industries, Inc. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Firemen & Oilers, Local 47., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  1/11/49. Issue: rates of pay - increase; holidays & holiday pay
- Astoria Casket Co. vs. United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners, Casket Makers Union, Local 3128., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  3/26/48. Issue: rates of pay - increase; holidays & holiday pay.
- Auto-Lite Battery Corp., Syracuse, NY vs. United Automobile, Aircraft & Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW)., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  4/16/46. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Avon Sale Co., Avon, MA vs. Brotherhood of Shoe & Allied Craftsmen, Rubber Sole & Heel Local., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  8/23/44. Issue: classification of jobs - rates of pay.
- Avon Sale Co., Avon, MA vs. Brotherhood of Shoe & Allied Craftsmen, Rubber Sole & Heel Local., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  2/20/46. Issue: rates of pay - new job.
- Avon Sale Co., Avon, MA vs. Int'l. Bro. of Oilers & Firemen, Local 47., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  6/13/49. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Avon Sale Co., Avon, MA vs. Int'l. Bro. of Oilers & Firemen, Local 47., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  9/14/49. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Babcox & Wilcox Co. vs. United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America (UERMWA), Local 439., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  1) 7/18/42. Issue: medical release - reinstatement - backpay. 2) 12/4/42. Issue: reclassification of jobs.
- Baldau Co., Fred W. vs. United Packing House Workers of America (UPWA), Local 11., 1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  1) 8/25/49. Issue: rates of pay discrimination. 2) 12/6/49. Issue: recall - delay in returning to work.
- Bali Brassiere Co. vs. Corset & Brassiere Workers Union, ILGWU, Local 32., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Issue: rates of pay - piecework vs. day work, rate revision. Preliminary decision 4/7/42, final decision 4/17/42.
- Barclay Mfg. Co. vs. Wholesale & Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  4/27/42. Issue: layoff - seniority - backpay.
- Batchelder & Snyder Co., Inc. vs. UPWA, Local 11., 1944 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  8/14/44. Issue: overtime - notice, breaks.
- Battle Creek Foundry Co. vs. Moulders & Foundry Workers of North America, Local 251., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  4/18/42. Issue: interest arbitration - rates of pay.
- Beggs & Cobb, Inc. vs. International Fur & Leather Workers Union of the U.S. & Canada, Local 22. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Issue: rates of pay - wage increases (no award, no date).
- Beko Spinning Mill vs. Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA) Local 15-D., 1946 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  9/20/46. Issue: 1) union shop 2) schedules of work - premium pay.
- Bell Aircraft Corp. vs. United Automobile, Aircraft & Agricultural Implement Workers of America, CIO, Local 999 (UAW)., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  3/4/47. Issue: discharge - interference w/production - union representative.
- Bendix Aviation Corp. vs. UAW, Local 387., 1945 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  1) 7/18/45. Issue: assignment of jobs - added duties, elimination of jobs. 2) 7/18/45. Issue: promotion - seniority. 3) 7/16/45. Issue: discharge - tardiness, leaving plant without permission.
- Benrus Watch Co. vs. Waterbury Brassworkers Union, Local 251, International Union of Mine, Mill & Smelter Workers (IUMMSW)., 1946 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  3/6/46. Issue: layoff - plant wide, departmental seniority.
- Bentley & Co., Inc. vs. Department of Woolens & Worsted Workers of the UTWA, Local 51., 1946 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  8/26/46. Issue: leave of absence - military leave, accrual of seniority during.
- Berkshire Street Railway Co. vs. Amalgamated Association of Street & Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employees of America, Division 496., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  4/9/48. Issue: interest arbitration - rates of pay.
- Beyda & Co., Inc. vs. Retail Dry Goods Employees Union, Local 1102., 1940 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  7/11/40. Issue: layoffs - lack of work.
- Bigelon Sanford Carpet Co. vs. TWUA, Local 2188., 1944 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  7/10/44. Issue: rates of pay - rates revision.
- Bijur Lubricating Corp. vs. UE, Local 1227., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  3/12/47. Issue: promotion - seniority.
- Bison Castings, Inc. vs. United Steelworkers of America (USW), Local 2875., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  9/4/48. Issue: discharge - improper personal conduct.
- Bloom & Son, Inc., Samuel vs. Joint Board of Cloak, Skirt & Dressmakers Union, ILGWU., 1945 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  6/11/45. Issue: financial responsibility - fringe benefits.
- Bonafide Genasco, Inc. vs. IUMMSU, Local 847., 1946 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  8/16/46. Issue: holiday pay.
- Boston & Maine Transportation Co. vs. Amalgamated Association of Street and Electric Street Railway and Motor Coach Employes of America, AFL, Local 1038., 1946 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  9/9/46. Issue: backpay award.
- Boston Royal Petticoat Co. vs. ILGWU, Local 229., 1941 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  2/10/41. Issue: discharge - substandard performance, union activity.
- Boston Sausage & Provision Co. vs. UPWA, Local 11., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  1) 5/29/42. Issue: discharge - unsatisfactory work - standards of production. 2) 2/7/46. Issue: discharge - work breaks. 3) 1/20/47. Issue: computation of overtime. 4) 11/10/48. Issues: a) supervisors & foremen - performance of bargaining unit work - layoffs
- Bourque Shoe Company vs. United Shoe Workers of America (USWA), Local 106., 1944 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  5/26/44. Issue: rates of pay - increase
- Brampton Woolen Co. vs. TWUA, Local 112., 1944 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  9/19/44. Issue: reinstatement following work stoppage
- Branch River Wool Combing Co. vs. TWUA, Local 390., 1942-1949 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  1) 6/25/42. Issue: work stoppage. 2) 9/21/42. Issues: added duties - past practice. 3) 12/8/42. Issue: compliance with award - insubordination, absenteeism. 4) 12/24/42. Issues: a) backpay b) elimination of jobs. 5) 8/25/43. Issues: a) reduction in force.
- Braun Baking Co. vs. Bakery Drivers Union, Local 485., 1941 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  3/5/41. Issue: work preference, seniority.
- Brewer Dry Dock Co. vs. Brewer Dry Dock Employees Association, Inc., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  3/1/48. Issue: discharge
- Brightwater Paper Co. vs. UMW, District 50, Local 12796., 1945 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  11/21/45. Issue: discharges - excessive absences - unsatisfactory work.
- Brockton Cut Sale Corp. vs. Cut Sale. Local. Brotherhood of Shoe and Allied Craftsmen., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  1) 9/24/42. Issue: wage increase. 2) 12/26/42. Issue: compliance with award
- Brockton Tool Co. vs. International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  8/20/48. Issue: upgrading.
- Brown Bros. Co. and United Furniture Workers of America, Local 154., 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  1) 11/4/47. Issue: discharge - union activity. 2) 9/14/48. Issue: a) discharge - disability. b) rate of pay - rate revision.
- Brown Co. vs. UMW, District 50, Local 12175., 1944 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  12/11/44. Issue: transfer - seniority.
- Brown Shoe Co. vs. UMW, District 50, Local 12677., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  1) 6/24/48. Issues: rate revisions - job reclassifications. 2) 9/13/48. Supplemental decision - 6/24/48.
- Brown Shoe Co. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 132-A., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  9/24/47. Issue: wage increases, incentive pay.
- Brown Shoe Co. vs. UMW, District 50, Local 12652., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  7/17/48. Issues: 1) bidding. 2-4) rate revision. 5) job security. 6) incentive pay. 7) discharge. 8-11) rate revision.
- Cameron Mfg. Corp., Emporium, PA vs. UE, Local 605., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  6/27/47. Issue: layoff - seniority.
- Campbell, A.S. Co., Inc. East Boston, MA vs. UE, Local 272., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  3/16/46. Issue: layoff - seniority.
- Campbell Soup Co., Camden, NJ vs. Food, Tobacco, Agricultural & Allied Workers Union of America, Local 80., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  5/2/46. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Carbone, C. & Co. Inc., Somerville, MA vs. Int'l. Bro. of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers of America (IBT), Local 25., 1950 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  1/16/50. Issue: contract modification.
- Casket Manufacturers Negotiating Committee vs. Casket Makers, Local 3128. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Issue: rates of pay - increase. No date, no decision.
- Celanese Corp. of America, Newark, NJ vs. UMW, District 50, Local 12666., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  1/25/47, 2/3/47. Issue: working conditions - safety. no decision
- Chicopee Mfg. Corp. vs. TWUA, Local 144., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  4/13/43. Issue: rates of pay - increase
- Cities Service Oil Co., Boston, MA vs. Oil Workers Int'l. Union, Local 366., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  5/21/45. Issue: discipline - layoff.
- Cogswell Mfg. Co. vs. UE, Local 238., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  5/2/45. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Cohen, H. & Co., Inc. vs. USW, Local 2237., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  1/16/43. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Cole - Hersee Co. vs. UE, Local 262., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  8/4/47. Issue: contract modification.
- Colonial Provision Co., Inc. vs. United Packinghouse Workers of America, Local 11., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  8/8/42. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Colonial Provision Co., Inc. vs. United Packinghouse Workers of America, Local 11., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  6/14/49. Issue: discipline -discharge.
- Commonwealth Shoe & Leather Co. vs. Bro. of Shoe & Allied Craftsmen, Mixed Local., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  8/8/42. Issue: rates of pay.
- Commonwealth Shoe & Leather Co. vs. Bro. of Shoe & Allied Craftsmen, Cutters Local., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  4/13/43. Issue: rates of pay.
- Connecticut Cabinet Corp. vs. Int'l. Assoc. of Machinists (IAM), Local 1913., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  12/27/47. Issue: rates of pay - retroactive pay.
- Continental Diamond Fibre Co. vs. UTWA, Local 58., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  5/31/45. Issue: standards of production - workload.
- Coronet Shoe Corp. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Joint Council No. 20., 1944 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  1/18/44.Issue: rates of pay.
- Corset & Brassiere Manufacturers Assoc. vs. Corset & Brassiere Workers' Union, Local 32., 1939 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Issue: strikes, slowdowns & work stoppages.
- Cranston Print Works Co. vs. UTWA, Local 2459., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  9/23/46. Issue: rates of pay.
- Cranston Print Works Co. vs. UTWA, Local 2459., 1950 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  2/8/50. Issue: discrimination - union activities & membership.
- Cranston Print Works Co. vs. UTWA, Local 2459., 1949 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  4/13/49. Issue: standards of production - workload.
- Cranston Print Works Co. vs. UTWA, Local 2459., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  11/29/47. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment.
- Cranston Print Works Co. vs. UTWA, Local 2459., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  10/14/47. Issue: union security.
- Crucible Steel Co. of America, Holcomb Steel Division vs. USW, Local 1277., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  7/27/42. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Crucible Steel Co. of America, Holcomb Steel Division, Sanderson Works vs. USW., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  8/13/42. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Curtiss-Wright Corp., Caldwell, NJ vs. IAM, Local 703., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  1/29/48. Issue: evaluation of job factors. no decision.
- Curtiss-Wright Corp, Propeller Division vs. IAM, Local 703., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  7/21-22/48. Issue: evaluation of job factors. no decision
- D&W Metal Products Co., Bronx, NY vs. UMW, United Construction Workers, Local 178., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  10/17/45. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Dan River Mills, Inc. vs. TWUA, Pittsylvania County Joint Board., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  12/5/46. Issue: training & trial period - rates of pay. no decision.
- Dan River Mills, Inc. vs. TWUA, Pittsylvania County Joint Board., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  3/25/47. Issue: standard of production - workload. no decision.
- Dan River Mills, Inc. vs. TWUA, Pittsylvania County Joint Board., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  2/27/47. Issue: rates of pay - transfers. no decision.
- Danielson & Co. vs. Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators & Paperhangers of America, Marine Painters Local 679., 1944 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  8/7/44. Issue: rates of pay - premium pay.
- Davega-city Radio, Inc. vs. Retail Employees Union, Local 850., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  11/4/41. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Danielson & Co. vs. TWUA, Local 477., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  5/10/46. Issue: lay off -seniority.
- Davis & Geck, Inc. vs. TWUA, Greater New York Joint Board., 1950 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  2/9/50. Issue: vacation pay - layoff.
- Decca Records, Inc. vs. UE, Local 430., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  5/20/46. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Devonsheer Melba Corp. vs. Bakery & Confectionery Workers Int'l. Union of America., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  6/6/46. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Dolphin Jute Mills vs. TWUA, Local 647., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  3/15/48. Issue: holidays & holiday pay.
- Doten Dunton Desk Co. vs. UFW, Local 136-B., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  2/19/46. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Doughnut Corp. of America vs. United Office & Professional Workers of America, Local 16., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  1/2/42. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Douglas, W.L. Shoe Co. vs. Brotherhood of Shoe & Allied Craftsmen, Vampers Local., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  4/27/45. Issue: rates of pay.
- Doyle Shoe Co. vs. Brotherhood of Shoe & Allied Craftsmen (BSAC), Finishers Local., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  11/16/42. Issue: rates of pay.
- Drake, George E. Baking Co. vs. Bakery Drivers' Union, Local 485., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  11/13/41. Issue: rates of pay - commissions.
- Dravo Corp., Pittsburgh, PA vs. Industrial Union of Marine & Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 61 (IUMSWA)., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  2/26/45. Issue: layoff - seniority.
- Dravo Corp., Pittsburgh, PA vs. Industrial Union of Marine & Shipbuilding Workers of America, Local 61 (IUMSWA)., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  2/26/45. Issue: reinstatement.
- Durez Plastics & Chemicals, Inc. vs. UE, Local 312., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  6/17/46 & 7/3/46. Issue: schedules of work - management rights. no decision.
- Durez Plastics & Chemicals, Inc. vs. UE, Local 312., 1947 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  12/17/47. Issue: holidays & holiday pay; rates of pay - Saturday, Sunday & holiday work
- Eaton, Charles A., Co. vs. BSAC, Stitchers Local., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  1/3/43. Issue: rates of pay.
- Eaton, Charles A., Co. vs. BSAC., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  10/21/42. Issue: rates of pay. Easton, Charles A., Co. vs. BSAC, Sole Fasteners Local. 12/26/42. Issue: rates of pay.
- Electric Boat Co. vs. Shipbuilders & Marine Engineers Union., 1944 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  9/11/44. Issue: definitions - job classification.
- Eaton, Charles A., Co. vs. BSAC, Lasters' Local., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  2/26/43. Issue: rates of pay.
- Employees Transit Lines, Inc. vs. Amalgamated. Assoc. of Street, Electric Railway & Motor Coach Employees of America, Division 1034., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  7/22/46. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Endicott Johnson Corp. vs. 7 toe Lasters., 1944 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  6/7/44. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment
- Endicott Johnson Corp. vs. United Shoe Workers of America, Local 83., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  12/12/45. Issue: rates of pay - increase.
- Endicott Johnson Corp. vs. Fifty Five Sole Cutters., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  5/28/45. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment.
- Endicott Johnson Corp. vs. Seventeen Dry Thread Vampers., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  1/10/45. Issue: rates of pay.
- Endicott Johnson Corp. vs. 18 Whole Lift Heel Building Operators., 1944 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  6/16/44. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment
- Endicott Johnson Corp. vs. Four Operators on "Reinforced Nailing" Operation., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  10/16/43. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment
- Endicott Johnson Corp. vs. Fifty-nine "Sole Cutting" Operators., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  8/16/43. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment.
- Endicott Johnson Corp. vs. Zig-Zag Stitch Operators., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  7/27/43. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment
- Endicott Johnson Corp. vs. Four "Fitters" or Stitchers., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  7/26/43. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment.
- Endicott Johnson Corp. vs. Seven "Pull-Last" Operators., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  7/26/43. Issue: rates of pay - adjustment
- Endicott Johnson Corp. vs. Thirty Regular Stitch Edge Operators., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 40)